

# **Sergey Markovich**

Pr. Stachki 221 82 Rostov-na-Donu ROS 344090 Russia **E-mail:** sergeymarkovich111@gmail.com **Website:** <a href="https://markvich111.github.io/">https://markvich111.github.io/</a>

## **ABOUT ME**

My name is Sergey Markovich.

I'm a full stack developer in building modern responsive web applications and using wide set of technologies.

Also I have a good experience with blockchain development like as smart contact development, dApp building, front end integration with smart contract using web3. I have strong knowledge in developing single page applications (SPA) with pixel perfect UI/UX design.

I'm a hardworking and dedicated professional front-end developer/user interface designer with a keen eye for detail and a determination to deliver the very highest quality. I take great pride in my work, and I always try to better myself with every project I work on.

I like to write semantic, cross browser compatible code by hand that is re-useable, maintainable and easy to understand.

Cheers!

## WORK EXPERIENCE

### Reservations. Inc

Feb 2017 — March 2019

Frontend Developer

Reservations. Inc

- Responsibilities: Develop new features, code review, Migrate from Gulp to Webpack 4
- Tools & Technologies: Angular.js, Webpack 4, Gulp, REST API, Swagger, Jira, Git

#### Your DS

Feb 2018 — Feb 2019

Frontend Developer

Your DS

- Responsibilities: Develop frontend with vanilia javascript/html/css, Integration with Laravel backend API
- Tools & Technologies : Javascript, Html, CSS, PHP, Laravel

# USEFULL, formerly Coffee Cup Collective

May 2019 — Oct 2020

Frontend Developer

USEFULL, formerly Coffee Cup Collective

- Responsibilities: Develop UX/UI based on CoreUI React Admin Panel. Layout of adaptive, cross-browser and high-loaded templates.
- Tools & Technologies : CoreUI Pro React license, REST API, Swagger, Reactstrap(Bootstrap 4), Kira, Scrum

## **Bushtracks Africa**

Jan 2021 — Apr 2021

Full Stack developer

Bushtracks Africa

Sergey Markovich

- Responsibilities: Layout of adaptive, cross-broswer and high-loaded templates.
  Develop new features, bug fixing
- Tools & Technologies : React.js, Node.js

### **World of Women**

Jan 2021 — Jul 2021

Full Stack developer

World of Women

- Built ERC721 based smart contract. Frontend development and integrated with smart contract
- Tools & Technologies : React.js, Web3.js, Solidity, NFT, IPFS, Truffle

## **Bored Ape Yacht Club**

Mar 2021 — Jul 2021

Full Stack developer

Bored Ape Yacht Club

- Built NFT, dApp solution Frontend development
- Tools & Technologies : React.js, Web3.js Solidity, NFT, IPFS, Truffle, Opensea

## The Sevens

May 2021 — Sep 2021

Blockchain developer

The Sevens

- Built NFT, smart contract development
- Tools & Technologies : Solidity, NFT, IPFS, Truffle, Opensea

## **EDUCATION**

## **Southern Federal University**

2010 - 2015

Bachelor of Computer Science (BCompSc), Computer engineering

## **INTERESTS**

### Sports, Travelling

## **SKILLS**

My stack technology area:

- ✓ Single Page Application (SPA) development 5 years
- ✓ Admin panel development 6 years
- ✓ Front End development 6 years
- ✓ Back End development 3 years
- ✓ Blockchain development 1 year
- ✓ Mobile app development 6 years

Program Language and Tools:

- ✓ HTML5, CSS3, SASS / SCSS / LESS preprocessors 6 years
- ✓ TypeScript, JavaScript (ES5+) 6 years
- ✓ PHP 7 years
- ✓ Angular 2+ (RxJS, NgRx) 3 years
- ✓ React (Redux, Saga, MobX) 4 years
- ✓ Vue.js (Vue2+) 2 years
- ✓ Node.js 2 years
- ✓ Solidity 1 year
- ✓ Rust 1 year
- ✓ Web3.js 1 year
- ✓ Truffle / Hardhat / OpenSea 1 year
- ✓ Objective C / Swift / Java Android / React Native 6 years

Sergey Markovich 2

- ✓ D3.js / Material UI / Bootstrap / Tailwind.css 3 years
- ✓ Webpack / Gatsby 3 years
- ✓ Unit testing: Jest 1 year
- ✓ AWS (EC2, RDS, s3) 2 years
- ✓ GitHub, GitLab, Trello, Jira, Asana 4 years

Sergey Markovich 3